<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.3.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-01-16T21:54:22-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Site11</title><subtitle>An website.</subtitle><author><name>yoyosammy</name><email>phrackingbits@gmail.com</email></author><entry><title type="html">TP-Link Kasa Indoor Pan/Tilt Smart Security Camera EC70</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/EC70/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="TP-Link Kasa Indoor Pan/Tilt Smart Security Camera EC70" /><published>2023-01-14T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2023-01-14T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/EC70</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/EC70/"><![CDATA[<h1 id="reverse-engineering-the-ec70-ip-camera">Reverse Engineering the EC70 IP Camera</h1>

<p>I decided I wanted to start looking into IP cameras and this one was
relatively cheap and had good reviews so I figured it was a good place
to start.</p>

<p><img src="../assets/images/camera.jpg" alt="EC70" /></p>

<p>After opening the camera up and inspecting the board I found some copper
test points that vaguely look like they might be uart and next to it
some port labeled ETH so maybe ethernet? I tried connecting an alligator
clip to flash chip in order to dump flash but I continuously kept
getting “chip is blank” so either I don’t know how to hook up the chip
or there is something stopping me from dumping flash.  So I guess it was
back to seeing if those test pins were uart or not.  I did some
connectivity tests and determined one to be ground (TP13) which was a good
start.  I connected my uart cable to a ground elsewhere on the board, powered on the board and
then held the RX wire onto each of the other test points until TP11 started
printing text.  So I was able to read the uart but I cannot type and
hold two wires on the RX and TX so I got and clip onto the uart TX and
then booted the camera up.  Then whenever I wanted to send a command I
manually held the TX wire to the RX test point (TP12).</p>

<p><img src="../assets/images/uartConnect.JPG" alt="uart" /></p>

<p>I also accidentally pulled the power off of the board so I had to
manually hook them up to power the device.</p>]]></content><author><name>yoyosammy</name><email>phrackingbits@gmail.com</email></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reverse Engineering the EC70 IP Camera]]></summary></entry></feed>